<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>ThirdWorldProgrammer Blog</title>
  <subtitle>This is the ThirdWorldProgrammer Project</subtitle>
  <id>https://www.thirdworldprogrammer.github.io</id>
  <link href="https://www.thirdworldprogrammer.github.io"/>
  <link href="https://www.thirdworldprogrammer.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2021-04-02T21:20:48+05:30</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Komefumi | Arjun Raju Pillai</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>My (Initial) Experiences With LeetCode</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.thirdworldprogrammer.github.io/articles/Competitive-Coding/experiences-with-leetcode.html"/>
    <id>https://www.thirdworldprogrammer.github.io/articles/Competitive-Coding/experiences-with-leetcode.html</id>
    <published>2021-04-02T21:20:48+05:30</published>
    <updated>2021-04-03T14:42:34+05:30</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Well, How do I say it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was pretty enlightening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I mean, yeah, it was hard going through many of the challenges. Or rather the learning cards. I started with arrays.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It often had it be that I finished maybe two problems in a day, or maybe one. Actually getting them to pass. A lot of time was spent thinking up solutions, and also with debugging.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It often had me spend the whole day accomplishing nothing else but this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Admittedly I have a lot on my mind and back then things were worse. It was so much more difficult to focus. Too difficult. I don't know how I managed to go that far with the paranoia and mental issues I was facing with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a good lesson to not repress things. And to face everything. Fears, pain, all of it. But it's necessary to find a good outlet.&lt;/p&gt;
Oftentimes with something that's a productive endeavor, we might be too focused on the outcome. Like, will spending time on this thing give me any benefit in the long run?
Will I maybe get a job with it? Maybe a career? We don't know. No one does. But something might happen. You need to be more engrossed with the process than the prize.
And then, you'll find fulfillment and yes, of course, you'll end up somewhere amazing. But it shouldn't be about money or with arbitrary goals.
&lt;p&gt;Now that I've written this, I think I see a need to spend more time with LeetCode. And put my hands where my mouth directs me to.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
